<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming on Sebastian D 🇨🇴</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/</link><description>Recent content in Programming on Sebastian D 🇨🇴</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction to programming</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/intro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/intro/</guid><description>What is programming? Well, I think that is a muddy question, because it encapsulates a wide range of activities with an even broader set of tools. If I had to give you a short definition it would be that programming is laying a set of rules for the computer to follow. It sounds extremely simple, but it is a process you can build upon and iterate layer over layer until these instructions create amazing software with complex functionality.</description></item><item><title>Robocup Virtual manipulator challenge</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/robocup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/programming/robocup/</guid><description>Resources Virtual manipulator challenge main page Video introduction source code Blog Other resources Pick-and-Place Workflow in Gazebo Using Point-Cloud Processing and RRT Path Planning Robocup@work team qualifications Robocup@home team qualifications Github getting started Design and Control of Robot Manipulators Get started with gazebo Objective Crate an algorithm for the robotic arm so it can sort properly the cans and bottles.
Cans must go into the green bin Bottles must go into the blue bin Config of this project A submodule is used the repository vision_ if you want to clone this repository use the command git clone --recurse-submodules https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>