<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Library on Sebastian D 游뻟릖</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/</link><description>Recent content in Library on Sebastian D 游뻟릖</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Of interest</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/ofinterest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/ofinterest/</guid><description>Because I seem to be pretty fond on lists, here are some more, of interesting institutions universities and people doing amazing work.
Universities ETH Z칲rich. Autonomous Systems Lab, Roland Siegwart robotics system lab DelftTU. Software architecture https://github.com/tudelft delftswa.github.io UPV (universidad politecnica de Valencia) URJC universidad rey juan carlos Universidad carlos iii madrid UC3M Stuttgart university, engineering cybernetics. Master of Science (MSc) focused in Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering from University of Stuttgar.</description></item><item><title>Quotebook</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/quotebook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/quotebook/</guid><description>This is a collection of quotes I found interesting in one way or another.
Literature The fact we live at the bottom of a deep gravity well, on the surface of a gas covered planet going around a nuclear fireball 90 million miles away and think this to be normal is obviously some indication of how skewed our perspective tends to be.
&amp;mdash; Douglas Adams
As칤 tambi칠n un orbe entero, con toda su peque침ez y su grandeza, puede ubicarse en una estrella que titila en la inmensidad del espacio, y as칤 como la mera ciencia humana es capaz de dividir un rayo de luz y analizar su composici칩n, as칤 tambien otras inteligencias m치s excelsas podr치n leer acaso en el tenue brillar de esta tierra nuestra todo pensamiento y toda acci칩n, todo vicio y toda virtud de cada uno de los seres responsables que la pueblan.</description></item><item><title>WatchList</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/watchlist/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/library/watchlist/</guid><description>Reading list So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You. Cal Newport Letters to a young scientist. Edward Osborne Wilson The Success of Open Source. Steven Weber Quantum country La era del diamante. Neal Stephenson The Martian. Andy Weir The man in the high castle. Philip K. Dick Masters of Doom. David Kushner Meditations. Marcus Aurelius My Philosophy of Industry. Henry Ford Bloc by Bloc: How to Organize a Global Enterprise for the New Regional Order.</description></item></channel></rss>