<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sebastian D 🇨🇴</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sebastian D 🇨🇴</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/meta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/meta/</guid><description>My name is Sebastian I am Mechatronics Student at Universidad &amp;hellip;.
Yeah, may be another presentation might be an overkill, I am guessing you have already read the about section which holds a formal presentation of who I am. This however is a more lay back version where I intend to explore and document the experiences while creating this website.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start from the beginning, I been thinking about writing for a long time but struggle to keep it up.</description></item><item><title>Robocup</title><link>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/matlab/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jsduenass.github.io/posts/matlab/</guid><description>Resources Virtual manipulator challenge main page Video introduction Robocup@work team qualifications Robocup@home team qualifications Github getting started Design and Control of Robot Manipulators Get started with gazebo This notes About the system The work is based on the vmware virtual machine provided by the github getting started. It contains:
ROS 2 Dashing desktop installation ROS Melodic desktop installation Gazebo robot simulator 9.0.0 Example Gazebo worlds for a simulated TurtleBot® 3 Checking the version of the software packages</description></item></channel></rss>